[Laughter]
folks that's why I believe in magic it's
been an interesting year I think for all
of us right there's a lot of political
disagreements in the world and I think
we I want to the interest of unifying I
think we can all agree on one thing
whatever you believe politically we can
agree that it's very funny
that four years ago there were a bunch
of people who were worried that Mitt
Romney was gonna ruin the world
remember those salad days seems cute now
doesn't it he lost that election in 2012
and we thought it was because he was too
rich and out of touch
[Applause]
gotta say I'm pretty sure that's not why
now
due to recent events here's the reason
that Mitt Romney lost in 2012 it's
because not because he's rich people in
America love that it's because he made
being that rich seemed like it wasn't
that much fun and people want to imagine
it being fun right say what you think
about Donald Trump
he's clearly having a good time with his
money
Mitt Romney made hundreds of millions of
dollars and then used it to have like
seven kids and never drink coffee
trying to make America boring again man
I was going on if you remember right
before the election there is that secret
video that leaked where Mitt Romney was
speaking to donors and he said his job
was only to care about the 47% of
Americans who pay their taxes and that
was a huge scandal at the time doesn't
that seem like a lot of Americans to
care about now
47% I probably care about eight
Americans and sorry Ike Donald Donald
Trump cares about 47 he doesn't care
about 47% of his own kids
[Music]
he's like I like the hot one in the kid
kinda and that's it subscribe to drive
our comedy for even more of the world's
largest collection of clean comedy